quizbox.com 2001-06-03

# QuizBox.com Statement of Privacy

## QuizBox.com statement of privacy

QuizBox.com is committed to protecting your online privacy. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can. In order to enhance your experience at our site we gather certain information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

### What information do we collect?

  * **PERSONALITY TESTS, RIDDLES AND PUZZLES**  
We do not collect answers to any of the personality tests, riddles, and puzzles on this site for any purpose. All of your answers are **completely anonymous and private**.
  *  **OPTIONAL REGISTRATION**  
We offer free, voluntary registration to users. By registering, users gain access to the Quiz Builder area, and they can take advantage of storing their own quizzes on this site.

During registration the user **is required** to supply an email address, their name, password of choice, and they must answer mandatory survey questions about their age and gender.

  *  **USAGE TRACKING**  
We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. QuizBox.com does not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

We also collect IP addresses and referring URLs for system administration and to report aggregate information to our sponsors and advertisers.

### What do we do with the information we collect?

QuizBox.com's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Web site. Such information also enables us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. Because QuizBox.com derives its revenue mainly from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keep our service free to users.

### With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?

QuizBox.com does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others. We use the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keep our service free. We do not share information about individual users with any third party.

### Forums

When disclosing personal information such as your actual name, e-mail address, etc in a discussion forum, that information may be collected and used by others. Although QuizBox.com respects the privacy of your messages, it makes no representation, warranties or commitments concerning our ability to keep your messages private in a discussion forum.

### External links

This site contains links to other sites. QuizBox.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Changes to our privacy policy

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.

### Who to contact

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to privacy@quizbox.com.

Children's safe use of this site
